deardoctor.com 2019-11-02

# Dentist, Dentistry & Oral Health Guide | Dear Doctor Dental Magazine

Welcome to deardoctor.com, the Web site of _Dear Doctor - Dentistry & Oral Health_ magazine, which is published by Dear Doctor, Inc. Dear Doctor does not control, and is not responsible for, any third-party site to which the Web site links.

You agree that your use of the Web site is subject to the following Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions may be modified at any time and from time to time. Continued access to the Web site by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Agreement.

**_If you do not agree with the Terms and Conditions, please do not use this Web site._**

**THE DEARDOCTOR.COM WEBSITE DOES NOT PROVIDE MEDICAL ADVICE.**

If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or 911 immediately.

The consumer health information on deardoctor.com (the "Website") is for informational and educational purposes only and is not a substitute for medical advice or treatment for any dental conditions. At times, this Website offers current, factual, and medically relevant answers to questions received from our users, however, these responses are only educational and informative in nature and cannot in any way be used to represent a complete analysis or diagnosis. The contents of the Website should not be interpreted as a recommendation for a specific treatment plan, product or dental care provider.

Nothing posted on this Website is intended to constitute professional advice for medical diagnosis or treatment. You should not use this Website to diagnose a medical or dental problem or disease and you should promptly seek professional medical or dental care if you have any concern about your health. Never disregard the advice of a dentist or health professional, or delay in seeking such advice, because of something you read on this Website. This Website should not be substituted for regular consultation and visits with your dental care provider. Users are urged to consult other sources as well as to obtain direct consultation with a dentist or dental specialist when making decisions about their health care.

Dear Doctor does not recommend or endorse any specific tests, physicians, products, procedures, opinions, or other information that may be mentioned on the website. Reliance on any information provided by Dear Doctor or others appearing on the website at the invitation of Dear Doctor, or other visitors to the website is solely at your own risk.

### Disclaimer of Representations and Warranties

The materials contained on the Web site are provided by Dear Doctor as a service to you for your noncommercial, personal use on an "as is" basis and may be used by you for information purposes only. You acknowledge that you are using the Web site at your own risk. Dear Doctor assumes no responsibility for error or omissions in these materials. Dear Doctor makes no commitment to update the information contained herein. Dear Doctor expressly disclaims any and all representations or warranties, express or implied, regarding the Web site, including without limitation the accuracy, completeness, or reliability of text, graphics, links, products and services, and other items accessed from or via the Web site, or that the Web site will be uninterrupted, error-free, or free of viruses or other harmful components. No advice or information given by Dear Doctor or any other party on the Web site shall create any warranty or liability. Under no circumstances shall Dear Doctor or any of its affiliates, or their respective officers, directors, employees, or agents be held liable for any damages, whether direct, incidental, indirect, special, or consequential, and including, lost revenues or lost profits, arising from or in connection with your use, reliance on, or performance of the information on the Web site.

### Downtime

Dear Doctor periodically schedules system downtime for maintenance and other purposes. Unplanned outages also may occur. Dear Doctor shall have no liability for the resulting unavailability of the Web site or for any loss of data or transactions caused by planned or unplanned system outages, or any outages of webhost providers or the Internet infrastructure and network external to the Web site.

### Copyright & Trademark

All materials published on the Web site are protected by copyright laws. None of the materials on the Web site may be reproduced, republished, distributed, transmitted, resold, displayed, broadcast, or otherwise exploited in any manner without the express written permission of Dear Doctor. Dear Doctor and other marks indicated on the Web site are the exclusive property of Dear Doctor, Inc. "Dear Doctor" is a registered trademark with the United States Patent & Trademark Office. Dear Doctor trademarks may not be used (i) in connection with any third party product or service; (ii) in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers; or (iii) in any manner that disparages or discredits Dear Doctor. Dear Doctor enforces its copyright and trademark interests to the fullest extent permitted under the law, and shall seek civil and criminal remedies where appropriate.

### User Generated Content

Dear Doctor may, through its forums, provide users an opportunity to post content to the Web site. Dear Doctor does not endorse or support the content posted by users. You shall not post or transmit any unlawful threatening, abusive, libelous, defamatory, obscene, vulgar, pornographic, profane, or indecent information of any kind, including without limitation any transmissions constituting or encouraging conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate and local, state, national, or international law, or infringe upon another's copyright or trademark. You are entirely and solely responsible for all content that you upload, post, or otherwise transmit via the Web site. Dear Doctor does not review the content posted by users and is not responsible for such content, however, Dear Doctor has the right to delete, move, or edit any content that violates this agreement or is otherwise objectionable as determined by Dear Doctor in its sole discretion and without notice.

### License

If you upload, post, or otherwise transmit content to the Web site, you acknowledge that you are granting Dear Doctor a license to Dear Doctor to use, edit, remove, modify, publish, transmit, and display your submission in any medium now existing or hereinafter invented, and for any purpose, including for commercial uses. You waive any moral rights you may have in having the submitted material edited, removed, modified, published, transmitted, or displayed in a manner not agreeable to you. You hereby acknowledge and agree that Dear Doctor shall have no obligation to compensate you in any way for any submission that you make.

### Indemnification

You agree to indemnify Dear Doctor and affiliates, and their officers, directors, employees, and agents, against, and to hold each of them harmless from, any and all claims and liabilities (including attorney's fees) that may arise from your submissions, from your unauthorized use of material obtained from the Web site, from your breach of these Terms and Conditions, and from any such acts arising through your use of the Web site.

### Featured Services

Dear Doctor is committed to providing visitors to its site with as many features as possible. The service providers that are featured on the Web site offer products and services that site visitors may find useful. In certain cases, Dear Doctor may have a business relationship with certain third parties that it selects as featured service providers. Dear Doctor is not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any advice or information given, or of any statement made, by the service providers, or for the content, services, products, or advertising on or available from their web sites, or for the availability and operations of their web sites.

### Monitoring

Dear Doctor has the right, but not the obligation, to monitor your use of the Dear Doctor Web site to determine compliance with these Terms and Conditions and any operating rules established by us and to satisfy any law, regulation, authorized government request or trade association guideline.

### Jurisdiction

You agree that any claim, action, or proceeding arising out of these Terms and Conditions, or your use of the Web site, shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York applicable to contracts to be wholly performed therein, and any action based on or alleging a breach of this Agreement must be brought in a state or federal court in New York. In addition, you agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts.

## Privacy Policy

### Web Site Users

From time to time, with your knowledge and consent, Dear Doctor collects personally identifiable information such as a name, postal address, E-mail address, telephone number, or credit card information.

### Use of Personal Information

Dear Doctor retains certain personally identifying information that is supplied by our Web site visitors. If you choose to give us personally identifying information at such time, such information will be retained by us and used only to provide you with products or services you have requested, or with additional information from Dear Doctor about Dear Doctor, its affiliates, or selected outside service providers whose products or services we feel may be of use to you. Any information from selected service providers will be transmitted by Dear Doctor so that the service providers will not have access either to your E-mail address or to your other personally identifying information, unless you provide them this information directly. We will not sell or rent any personally identifying information obtained through the Web site to any other company or service provider.

If, at some point after giving Dear Doctor your personally identifying information, you do not wish to continue to receive additional information from Dear Doctor, its affiliates, or selected outside companies, in general, you may opt out by E-mailing optout@deardoctor.com and put the words "remove my name" in the subject line of your E-mail; in the case of our E-mail newsletters, you also may follow the procedures at our E-mail newsletter registration page.

From time to time, the personally identifying information that you provide to us may be shared with our suppliers or service providers who assist us in maintaining and managing our newsletters, our archives, our online content, our online discussion forums, and other activities on the Web site. Such suppliers or service providers may use your personally identifying information only in the course of providing services to Dear Doctor, but they may not use such information for other purposes.

While your individual information is protected as discussed above, Dear Doctor reserves the right to use such individual information to create aggregated, anonymous data about users in order to develop statistics about activity on and visitors to the Web site. In addition, Dear Doctor may disclose personal information if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Web site; or (4) protect the personal safety, property, or rights of our users or the public.

### Contests

From time to time, we also may offer contests or other promotions involving marketing or advertising partners. If you choose to participate in one of these contests or promotions, you'll have to provide some personally identifying information about yourself. We use this information to verify eligibility and to notify winners. We may share this information with co-sponsors of the contest or other promotional partners. We do not control these third parties' privacy practices, and our Privacy Policy does not apply to their collection and use of personal information. We urge you to review their privacy policies and learn how they will use the information before participating. If you don't want us to collect the information requested in the promotion, or to provide it to our co-sponsors or partners, please do not participate in the contest or promotion.

### Cookies & IP Information

"Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your computer. Cookies do not contain information that is, in itself, personally identifying. Cookies may be placed on your computer in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to calculate unique site visitors, and to track usage throughout our site. Other uses include placement of cookies to make the login process more convenient for users of our E-mail newsletters, our archives, our online content, and our online discussion forums. In addition, some advertisers may place cookies on your computer. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of various features on our site that are available to other visitors.

When you use our site, we may also collect your browser type, access time, and/or Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and keep records of this information. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. Your IP address does not tell us who you are. Like the IP address, none of this other information identifies you personally; we collect it for aggregate reporting on site activity that we, and our advertisers, may use. The aggregate information helps to understand our audience and confirm the value of the advertising on our website.

### Credit Card Information

When you make a purchase, we ask you to provide your credit card information so that we can process your payment. During the ordering process, such credit card information is transmitted to Dear Doctor or to one of our suppliers or service providers. In both cases, credit card information is then transmitted to third-party credit card processors and card issuers that must use your information to process your order.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

No one under the age of 13 should provide any personal information. Dear Doctor does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without verified parental consent prior to collection. In the event that we learn that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete this information from our database as quickly as possible. If you believe the Web site has any information about anyone under 13, please contact us at webmaster@deardoctor.com.

### Security

The personally identifiable information we collect is securely stored within our database, and we use standard, industry-wide procedures such as encryption and firewalls for protecting your information. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a message you post to any message board, discussion group, or other public posting area on our sites is available to anyone with Internet access.

### Unauthorized Use/Hacking

Dear Doctor's Web site and system are made available for lawful activities by authorized users only. Any person using the site without authority or for any unlawful activity are subject to having his or her activities monitored, recorded, investigated, examined and/or disclosed by or to Dear Doctor and its agents, and law enforcement. Dear Doctor may also monitor, record and disclose the activities of authorized users.

### Modifications

Dear Doctor reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the site or any of the services offered therein following any such posting will constitute your acceptance of all changes.
